kurtgeiger.com 2015-10-24

# Cookies & Privacy | Kurt Geiger

Kurt Geiger Limited ("we" and "us") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide an improved shopping experience, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy. You can visit the Website without disclosing any personally identifiable information about yourself. This notice should be read in conjunction with the terms & conditions of use for Kurt Geiger Ltd (the "Website") of which it forms part (the "Terms"). By using this Website or submitting information to us through or in connection with this Website, you signify your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you must not use this Website or submit information to us through or in connection with this Website.

## The information we collect and how we use it

  * We will use, store or otherwise process any personal information that relates to and identifies you, including but not limited to your name, postal address (for billing and delivery), e-mail address, telephone number, and any other information collected on registration with the Website, on placing an order and through surveys to the extent reasonably necessary to provide the products and services that are available through our Website to you by us. We process this information for the purpose of:
  * Dealing with your enquiries and orders.
  * Providing and personalising our products and services.
  * Compiling your profile.
  * Administering account records.
  * Processing your payment.
  * Maintaining information as a reference tool or general resource.
  * Carrying out market research campaigns.
  * Additionally we use this information to contact you via email, post, SMS and phone.

We also gather this information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring Website usage and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify you. You may from time to time wish us to provide you with information about our Website or any other service or products including those of third parties which we think may be of interest to you. Please tick the appropriate box if you wish to receive information about: our products and services services offered jointly with or on behalf of other organisations. Alternatively, you may ask us to provide you with information about our products and services, or services offered jointly with or on behalf of other organisations, by sending us an e-mail at [customerservice@kurtgeiger.com](mailto:customerservice@kurtgeiger.com), calling us on [+44 (0) 207 781 7480](tel:+44 \(0\) 207 781 7480) or writing to us at the following address: Kurt Geiger Limited, 24 Britton Street, London, EC1M 5UA. You may also visit your account details and change your communications options. Click here to go to your account. If you stop using the Website or your permission to use the Website is terminated, we may continue to use and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy (as amended from time to time) and as permitted by law. However, if you wish us to stop e-mailing you with information in connection with the Website, please send your request in accordance with paragraph 4 below. 

## Information security 

The Internet is not a secure medium. However, we have put in place various security procedures as set out in this policy. All your card details are passed from your browser to [SECPay] using secure server software (ssl) encryption. [SECPay] use secure server software (ssl) encryption systems. Your user account area is protected by your user name and password, which you should never divulge to anyone else. Please be aware that communications over the Internet, such as emails/webmails are not secure unless they have been encrypted. Your communications may route through a number of countries before being delivered - this is the nature of the World Wide Web/Internet. We cannot accept responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal information that is beyond our control. We believe that we have appropriate policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control (having regard to the type and amount of that data) from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All of our employees and data processors that have access to, and are associated with, the processing of your personal information are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' information. We ensure that your information will not be disclosed to government institutions or authorities except if required by law or when requested to by regulatory bodies or law enforcement organisations.

## To whom will your information be disclosed?

Your information may, for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, be disclosed for processing to:

  * Our employees.
  * Our affiliates.
  * Our group companies and their employees.
  * Successors in title to our business.
  * Third party consultants, contractors or other service providers who may access your personal information when providing services (including but not limited to IT support services) to us.
  * Government bodies and law enforcement agencies and in response to other legal and regulatory requests.
  * Auditors or contractors or other advisers auditing, assisting with or advising on any of our business purposes, in any jurisdiction where we operate.

## Your rights in relation to your information

You can write to us at any time to obtain a copy of your information and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Where appropriate, you may have your personal information erased, rectified, amended or completed. Please write to Kurt Geiger Limited, 24 Britton Street, London, EC1M 5UA. Please quote your name and address. We should be grateful if you would also provide brief details of the information of which you would like a copy or which you would like to be corrected (this helps us to more readily locate your data). We will require proof of your identity before providing you with details of any personal information we may hold about you. We will charge ten [10] pounds to cover the administration costs involved in providing you with a copy of your information.

## Cookies

Pieces of information transferred to your computer's hard disk from a website are known as cookies. They allow our Website to store information about your browsing patterns, making the Website more useful to you. Many major sites use cookies: in fact, they are commonly used throughout the Internet to offer personalised services. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. Each time you use our Website, the cookie is accessed. This way, we can track the features you use and the pages and content that you view on the Website to help personalise your experience. You may disable cookie support on your browser but be aware that by doing so, you will lose certain features that require a cookie to work properly. We may use the information collected by the cookie to provide us with various statistics without identifying any individual. Please contact us at [customerservice@kurtgeiger.com](mailto:customerservice@kurtgeiger.com) if you require information about disabling any cookies on the Website [or, for more information generally about cookies go to [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)]. You can also clear any cookies stored on your computer through the 'Tools' menu in your internet browser.

First party cookies are displayed in the below table.

Cookie name | Cookie expiry | Cookie purpose  
---|---|---  
nowelcomepopup | 47 Years | With the launch of our Kurt Geiger Welcome program. This cookie is used to determine whether a visitor had been displayed with the welcome program popup windows previously.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Browser closed | When browsing any of our product listing pages, this cookie remembers what filtering was applied on previous page views, to enhance the browsing experience.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | Browser closed | This cookie remembers what products were viewed by the customer on previous page views, to enhance the browsing experience  
CART | 1 hour | A unique id that is associated with a customer's shopping bag is kept in this cookie. This is basically so that our website has got access to this information at all times throughout a customer's visit.  
persistent_shopping_cart | Browser closed | This cookie remembers what products were added into your shopping basket, to enhance the browsing experience  
CUSTOMER | 1 hour | Once a user is logged in, this cookie remembers a unique id associated with that customer's session, so that the website has got access to it at all times throughout the customer's visit.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | 1 hour | Once a user is logged in, this cookie remembers a unique id associated with that customer's group that they have been placed in, so that the website has got access to it at all times throughout the customer's visit.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | 1 hour | This cookie remembers your login details to keep you logged in when returning to the site, to enhance the browsing experience  
WISHLIST | 1 hour | This cookie remembers a unique id associated with a customer's wishlist, if the customer had created a wishlist during a particular visit. This is so that the website has got access to it at all times throughout the customer's visit.  
WISHLIST_CNT | 1 hour | This cookie remembers a unique id associated with the amount of items in a customer's wishlist, if the customer had created a wishlist during a particular visit. This is so that the website has got access to it at all times throughout the customer's visit.  
frontend | 1 hour | This cookie contains a unique id relating to a customer's session on our website. This allows the website to provide continuity between customer visits.  
COUNTRY_BANNER_HIDE | Browser closed | This cookie determines if you have already closed the sites switcher banner.  
is_returning | 5 years | This cookie is used to remember if the customer has visited the site before and will note you as a returning visitor or new visitor.  
CACHED_FRONT_FORM_KEY | Browser closed | This cookie ensures onsite forms are not submitted by someone outside of the website.  
LAST_CATEGORY | Browser closed | This cookie is used to store the customers last visited category and notes the category id which was last viewed.  
COUNTRY | 5 years | This cookie remembers which country the customer has selected from country selector to ensure the customer has an optimum shopping experience.  
mp__utma | 2 years | This cookie is used to enable the functionality provided by Google Analytics. This software allows us to analyse visitor information.  
mp__utmb | 30 minutes | This cookie is used to enable the functionality provided by Google Analytics. This software allows us to analyse visitor information.  
mp__utmc | Browser closed | This cookie is used to enable the functionality provided by Google Analytics. This software allows us to analyse visitor information.  
mp__utmz | 1 month | This cookie is used to enable the functionality provided by Google Analytics. This software allows us to analyse visitor information.  
_ga | 2 years | This cookie is used to enable the functionality provided by Google Analytics. This software allows us to analyse visitor information  
_gali | 1 minute | This cookie is used to enable the functionality provided by Google Analytics. This software allows us to analyse visitor information  
_gat | 10 minutes | This cookie is used to enable the functionality provided by Google Analytics. This software allows us to analyse visitor informations  
_gat_rollup | 10 minutes | This cookie is used to enable the functionality provided by Google Analytics. This software allows us to analyse visitor information  
vee24.testCookie | Browser closed | This cookie is used to enable the online chat functionality and allows us to analyse the use of online chat.  
v24s_kurtgeiger | Browser closed | This cookie is used to enable the online chat functionality and allows us to analyse the use of online chat  
v24u_kurtgeiger | 10 years | This cookie is used to enable the online chat functionality and allows us to analyse the use of online chat  
vee24.autoNudgeRules | Browser closed | This cookie is used to enable the online chat functionality and allows us to analyse the use of online chat  
vee24.nudgeReceived.timeout | Browser closed | This cookie is used to enable the online chat functionality and allows us to analyse the use of online chat  
vee24.nudgeReceived.timestamp | Browser closed | This cookie is used to enable the online chat functionality and allows us to analyse the use of online chat  
vee24.numberOfNudgesShown | Browser closed | This cookie is used to enable the online chat functionality and allows us to analyse the use of online chat  
vee24.testCookie | Browser closed | This cookie is used to enable the online chat functionality and allows us to analyse the use of online chat  
vee24.userIsActive | Browser closed | This cookie is used to enable the online chat functionality and allows us to analyse the use of online chat  
  
Third party cookies are displayed in the below table.

Partner name | What their cookies are used for  
---|---  
Facebook | On our product detail pages we provide the customer with the capability to 'Like' our products on their Facebook social page. We do not have any control over these cookies, as they are whole fully managed by Facebook.  
  
## Your consent

By submitting any personal information (including, without limitation, your payment and contact/delivery details) to us, you consent to the use of information as set out in this policy. We reserve the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy and if we do so we will post the changes on this page. It is your responsibility to check the Privacy Policy every time you submit information to us or place an order. Use will signify that you agree to any such changes. In the event the purpose is for processing change, then we will contact you as soon as practicable and seek your consent where such notification relates to a new additional purpose for processing. Owing to the global nature of the Internet infrastructure, the information you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area. Countries outside of the EEA may not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. However, we have taken the steps outlined above to try and protect the security of your information.

## The Data Protection Act 1998

Kurt Geiger Limited is registered as a Data Controller under the terms of the Data Protection Act 1998 and we ensure we comply with all the protection the Act affords to you. Our registration number is Z6823882.

## Use of your personal information submitted to other websites

We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites even if you accessed the third party website using links from our Website. We recommend that you check the policy of each website you visit and contact the owner or operator of such website if you have concerns or questions.

## Further information

For further information from us on data protection and privacy or any requests concerning your personal information please write to Kurt Geiger Limited, 24 Britton Street, London, EC1M 5UA or email us at [customerservice@kurtgeiger.com](mailto:customerservice@kurtgeiger.com).
